Yerassilova Gaukhar

29 years old

+7 (775) 9994224 gaumus.work@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://muse775.github.io/GY_portfolio/

I am a beginner web developer with basic knowledge of HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript. Previously I've been working in the oil and gas sector for more than 5 years, mainly in administrative positions. At the moment I am changing my professional sphere since I find myself being fascinated by web development and programming. I suppose that programming is a great platform to fully realize my potential and apply personal, analytical skills and advanced knowledge of foreign languages to become a better professional.

Current goals:

- To work as part of a team;
- To improve my knowledge and competence in web development;
- To become a professional front-end developer.

Key Skills

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, SASS/SCSS/LESS, Gulp/Webpack, Photoshop, Figma

Education and professional development

2020	Johns Hopkins	University
------	---------------	------------

Coursera.org, HTML, CSS, and Javascript for Web Developers

2020 University of Michigan

Coursera.org, Interactivity with JavaScript

2020 Arizona State University

Coursera.org, Business English: Management and Leadership

2011 Kazakh State University of International Relations and World Languages

Almaty, Oriental studies

Work experience

2015-2019 KazInRuss-trading LLP

Almaty

Business Assistant to General Manager

2012-2015 Independent translation Agencies

Almaty/Astana

Freelance translator

2011-2013 KazTransOil JSC

Astana

Assistant of Deputy General Director for Business Support

2007-2008 Ordamed Central Asia Inc.

Almaty

Interpreter

Languages

Russian — Native

Kazakh — Native

English — Fluent

Japanese — Intermediate

Spanish — Elementary